patrika.tv 2016-03-25

# Patrika TV | Privacy Policy |

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection And Use**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be  
used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name and phone number (“Personal Information”).

**Log Data**

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may  
include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other  
statistics.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to  
your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a  
cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our  
Service.

**Security  **

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the  
Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to  
protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Links To Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you  
will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you  
visit.

**Disclaimer**

Patrika.tv is not a part or affiliated with www.patrika.com website and any other patrika group websites. 

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy  
Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are  
effective when they are posted on this page.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
